

EUGENIE UWIMANA

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

PROFIL

I am a junior web developer, flexible with great communication skills. Always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges, after working 8 years in retail, I decided it was time for something new and refreshing. Thanks to my course at Becode, I have learned how to develop static and dynamic web pages using HTML, CSS, JS and PHP. I also have a basic working knowledge of: Git, Bootstrap, MySQL database, NodeJS, Express and MongoDB.

CONTACT

+32 47 00 17 330



ugenie11987@gmail.com



38 rue du Roetaert 1180 Uccle



(IM) www.linkedin.com/in/e-j-uwimana

SKILLS

Coding Languages:

HTML5 | CSS | JavaScript | PHP

Software:

Node.js | Git | VSC | MySQL | PHPmyadmin

Framework:

Bootstrap | Express | Material UI

LANGUAGES

English | French | Kinyarwanda

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Sopra Steria, Eurocontrol, Brussels

FEB 2021 - APRIL 2021 (INTERNSHIP)

- *Renovating user interface web app
- *Material UI, Git, CSS Frameworks, Mongo DB.
- *JavaScript libraries and Frameworks (React, Express).
- *Front & Back-end problem solving.

BeCode. BeCentral. Brussels

2020 - APRIL 2021

- *Creating static & dynamic web pages
- *Created a responsive franchise Restaurant webpage
- *Created a streaming site in htm://css, JavaScript and PHP
- *Front & Back-end problem solving.

Gucci - Sales/Visual Merchandiser

2019 - 2020

Ensure the store is tidy and well run (Presentation, Merchandising).

EDUCATION

BeCode, BeCentral, Brussels

2019 - PRESENT

Web Development Course

London Metropolitan University, London, UK

2006 - 2009

Digital Media Design

HOBBIES

Coding | Traveling | Sports | Cooking | Interior Deco